Weird day. We woke up this morning to
a car that had just drove down the road,
hit the mailbox, hit the trash can, blew
the trash can in the neighbor's yard.
There's the little mailbox. That side's
cracked. Lid's all busted over on that
top side. And so, I went to the other
house to go grab the ladder. And when I
pulled back into the Jesus house, some
little weird man had just pulled in as
well. Like, he's in his little tie dye
hippie shirt, little long-haired hippie.
And I was like, "What the heck?" And he
starts unloading out of the back of his
truck a new mailbox and a new post. He
said, "I saw you guys' post this
morning. I just wanted to help out." And
we saved a baby bird this morning. It's
going to be okay.
It's going to be okay.
It should be okay.